INVENTORY TO THE PIERCE FAMILY PAPERS, 1841-1940 D-022
University of California, Davis General Library, Dept. of Special Collections
- George W. Pierce, Jr., 1864-1931; Series 3.; 1328 Linear Feet
  - Printed Material, n.d., 1867-1930; Subseries 3.6.; 433 items
    - Travel, n.d., 1867-1930; Subseries 3.6.7.; 121 items
      - Japan, ca. 1929; 11 items
        - Japan; brochures, pamphlets, and program in envelope labeled, "Japan;" ca, 1929; 11 items (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - New Zealand, n.d., 1 item
        - Brochure, n.d., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Palestine, n.d., 1 item
        - Book: Trumper, V. L., "Historical Sites in Palestine with a Short Account of Napoleon's Expedition to Syria," Cairo: Nile Mission Press, n.d., 1 vol. (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - The Philippines, n.d., 1 item
        - Pamphlet. "Manila and the Philippine Islands," Manila: The Philippine Education Company, n.d., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Scotland, n.d., 2 items
        - Book and map., 2 items (Box 7, Folder 37)
          "Macdonald's tourists' guide to Edinburgh and South-east of Scotland," Edinburgh, Scotland: Macdonald, William and Company, n.d.
      - Spain, 1924; 3 items
        - Book, receipt, and note., 3 items (Box 7, Folder 38)
          Calvert, A. F., "The Traveler's Handbook for Spain," London: Cook, Thomas and Son, 1924.
      - Switzerland, 1923-1924; 3 items
        - Book; Heinemann, F., "Lucerne: Lake of Lucerne and its Environs," Official Enquiry Office,., 1923; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 39)
        - Brochures, ca., 1924; 2 items (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Turkey, 1923-1924; 2 items
        - Book; "Vues de Constantinople," ca., 1924; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 41)
        - Pamphlet; "Tourist Guide to Constantinople, Robert College and Constantinople Woman's College," New York: Near East Colleges, ca.., 1923; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - United States, n.d., 1875-1925; 48 items
        Printed travel material related to the United States and collected by George W. Pierce, Jr. is arranged alphabetically by state. Within the category for each state, the materials are arranged by their format such as: broadsides, brochures, books, envelopes, lists, maps, menus, pamphlets, programs, schedules, and tickets and passes.
        - Alaska, n.d., 1923-1925; 18 items
          - Brochures, n.d., 1923-1925; 17 items (Box 7, Folder 43)
          - Pamphlet. Cordova Chamber of Commerce, "Via Cordova Alaska," Cordova, AK: Alaska Daily Times, n.d., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 44)
        - California, n.d., 1875-1925; 8 items
          Printed material related to travel in California is made up of an undated brochure about Camp Agassiz and Fallen Leaf Lodge in the Lake Tahoe area, a 1925 Northern California automobile road map, schedules, and tickets and passes. One undated schedule is for the Lake Tahoe Railway and Transportation Company route from Truckee, CA to Tahoe City, CA. Another undated schedule is for trips from San Francisco, CA to the Barlett Springs resort as provided by the San Francisco and North Pacific Railway or the Southern Pacific Railway. The tickets and passes include a ticket, business card, and envelope related to an 1875 trip from San Francisco, CA to Monterey, CA on the Goodall, Nelson and Perkins' Steamship Line. The other item that is part of the tickets and passes category is an 1899 Lompoc and Santa Barbara Stage Company pass for George W. Pierce, Jr. and wife on the account of the Glen Alpine Springs resort.
          - Brochure, n.d., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 45.1)
          - Map, 1925; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 45.2)
          - Schedules, n.d., 2 items (Box 7, Folder 45.3)
          - Tickets and Passes, 1875-1899; 4 items (Box 7, Folder 45.4)
        - Colorado, 1892; 1 item
          - Manitou Grand Caverns, broadside, ca. 1892; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 46)
        - Hawaii, n.d., 1917-1923; 19 items
          - Book; Logan, D., "All about Hawaii," Boston, MA: Chapple Publishing Company,., 1921; 4 items (Box 7, Folder 47)
            1 book and 3 leaves ship's letterhead.
          - Brochures, n.d., 1921-1923; 7 items (Box 7, Folder 48)
          - Envelope, n.d., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 49)
          - Lists of passengers and menus, S. S. Matsonia, March 7, 1923-March 13, 1923; 4 items (Box 7, Folder 50)
          - Pamphlet; Alexander, W. D., "A Short Synopsis of the Most Essential Points in Hawaiian Grammar," Honolulu, HI: Thrum, Thomas G.,., 1920; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 51)
          - Pamphlet; Kinney, H. W. and L. W. de Vis-Norton, "The Island of Hawaii," Hilo Board of Trade,., 1917; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 52)
          - Program, 1923; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 53)
        - New York
          - Pamphlet., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 54)
            "Niagara in Summer and Winter," Niagara Falls, NY: Nicklis, E. E., n.d.
        - Washington
          - Book; Barnes, A. H., "Our Greatest Mountain and Alpine Regions of Wonder," National Park Arts Series,., 1911; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Multiple Destinations, n.d., 1903-1929; 23 items
        Printed travel materials (collected by George W. Pierce, Jr.) that could not be categorized under the heading of one state or one country are held in this file. These materials are records of travel to multiple destinations and include a book, brochures, a map, a newsletter, a newspaper, and a ticket stub. Many of these items relate to cruises and tours.
        - Book; "The Shasta Route in All of its Grandeur," Chicago, IL: Teich, Curt and Company, n.d., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 13)
        - Brochure:Dollar Steamship Lines, 4 brochures, 2 envelopes, 1926; 6 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Brochure; Cook, Thomas and Son, 1927-1929; 2 brochures (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Brochure; United American Lines, 1925-1926; 3 brochures (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Brochures; Various Companies, 1922-1926; 6 brochures (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Map, route of the cruise, n.d., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 5.1)
        - Newsletter; "The Empress Cruise News," Canadian Pacific's Empress of Australia, No. 22,., Jan. 9, 1929; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 5.2)
        - Newspaper; "Woodland Daily Democrat,"., Nov. 17, 1924; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - Ticket Stub, Feb. 20, 1903; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 5.3)
    - University of California, 1873-1928; Subseries 3.6.8.; 17 items
      The subseries University of California is composed of printed materials related to the University of California and collected by George W. Pierce, Jr. These University of California materials are divided into 3 categories: Alumni Association, College of Agriculture, and Various. Within these subject categories items are organized by format such as a certificates, programs, a ticket, a bulletin, a flier, reports, clippings, a course schedule, and a diploma. Some highlights of these materials are a certificate for Pierce's lifetime membership in the University of California, Alumni Association, programs relating to Picnic Day 1912 and an 1899 Farmers' Institute, and Pierce's diploma from the University of California. The 1873/1874 University of California yearbook belonging to George W. Pierce, Jr. was separated from the Pierce Family Papers and can be found in the reading room of the Special Collections Department of the Shield's Library under the call number LD 777 B5 1873/1874.
      - University of California, Alumni Association, 1891-1897; 4 items
        - Certificate, Jan. 1, 1895; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 6.1)
        - Programs, Oct. 9, 1897; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 6.2)
        - Ticket, June 24, 1891; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 6.3)
      - University of California, College of Agriculture, 1899-1920; 6 items
        - Bulletin; Shaw, G. W., "How to Increase the Yield of Wheat in California," Bulletin No. 211, Berkeley, CA: The University Press,., 1911; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 7)
        - Flier; University Farm, incomplete date, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 8.1)
        - Program; Farmers' Institute; Danville, CA, Feb. 8-9, 1899; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 8.2)
        - Program; Fourth Annual Basket Picnic, University Farm, Davis, CA, May 11, 1912; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 8.3)
        - Report; Hunt, T. F., "Observations on the Recent Agricultural Inquiry in California," Berkeley, CA: University of California, College of Agriculture, ca.., 1917; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Report; "Results of the Investigations on Deciduous Fruits, Olives, Figs, Nuts, and Fruit Products for the Year Ending June 30, 1920," University of California, College of Agriculture, ca.., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Various, University of California, 1873-1928; 7 items
        - Clippings, 1920-1928; 3 items (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - Course Schedule, 1873; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 11.1)
        - Diploma,., 1875; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Programs, 1928; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 11.2)
    - Other Printed Material, n.d., 1867-1930; Subseries 3.6.9.; 63 items
      The Other Printed Material subseries is made up of 63 items (1867-1930) of printed material collected by George W. Pierce, Jr. These items did not seem to fit into the subject categories by which the rest of Pierce's printed material is arranged. The items in the Other Printed Material subseries are arranged by format of material such as broadsides, brochures, cards, clippings, directions, fliers, newsletters, newspapers, and programs. Subjects covered by the material in this subseries are varied and range from agricultural technology to household items and local elections to Arizona copper mining. The broadsides advertise Frye's Self Supporting Farm Gate, n.d.; The Great Yaqui Valley, $25.00 per acre, n.d.; and Truman's Improved Iron Harrow, Jackson and Truman, n.d. Directions are for The Adjusto Collar Clasp, n.d.; Eveready Tie, ca. 1920; Fisher's Patent Prairie Mower Knife Grinder, n.d.; Hale's Patent Meat Cutter and Stuffer, n.d.; a Wax Cylinder Record Player, n.d.; and the Gerrish Submerged Force Pump, Linworth, Kellog and Rail, n.d. The fliers in this subseries feature Dr. E. C. Abbey's cures and books, n.d.; an automatic derrick by Brown and Donnenwirth of Davisville, CA, ca. 1902; The Dixon Creamery, n.d.; a miniature copy of the assessment roll map of San Francisco, CA by Deffebach and Company Printers with an advertisement for Boyce Street Car Advertiser, n.d.; the Regular Democratic Ticket for delegate to the County Convention, Yolo County, CA, n.d.; the Regular Republican Ticket, Yolo County, CA, North Putah Precinct, various offices including George W. Pierce, Jr. for Member of the California State Assembly, ca. 1898; Smith's Form-A-Truck, ca. 1915; and Street Railways Advertising Company, 1922. The newspapers include a copy of the May 7, 1920 "Winters Express" and of the Feb. 11, 1925 "Woodland Daily Democrat" with articles about the Indian Valley Dam site, irrigation, the Yolo County Power and Water Company, Clear Lake, and storms. The Feb. 5, 1912 "Woodland Daily Democrat" mentions Dixwell Lloyd Pierce's high school standing.
      - Broadsides, n.d., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Broadside, Oversize, n.d., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Brochures, n.d., 1900-1915; 9 items (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Bulletin; "Facts about the War," Paris: Paris Chamber of Commerce,., Jan. 5, 1915; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Cards, n.d.; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 15.1)
      - Certificate; Office of the State Veterinarian, State of California, 1908; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 15.2)
      - Clippings, n.d., 1911-1930; 15 items (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Directions, n.d., 1920; 5 items (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Directions, Oversize, n.d., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Fliers, n.d., 1898-1922; 8 items (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Funeral notice for J. Eugene LaRue, 1906; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 19.1)
      - Letterhead, n.d., 1910; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 19.2)
      - Newsletter; "The Domestic Economist," Sacramento, CA and Virginia City, NV: Dale and Company,., 1867; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Newsletter; "Key System News," Oakland, CA: San Francisco-Oakland Terminal Railways,., Dec. 29, 1921; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Newspaper; "Arizona Range News," Special Copper Edition, Willcox, AZ:., Oct. 6, 1922; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Newspapers; "Pacific Rural Press;", pp. 27-28, 41-42 and, pp. 143-146, 155, 158, 160-161., Jan. 12, 1884 Feb. 19, 1887; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Newspaper; "The Winters Express,"., May 7, 1920; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 12.1)
      - Newspapers; "Woodland Daily Democrat.", Feb. 5, 1912, Feb. 11, 1925; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 12.2)
      - Order Form, 1904; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Pamphlet; Phelan, J. D., "Japan and the Shantung Affair: Keep the Orientals in Asia," The League of Nations, Washington, D. C.: Government Printing Office,., 1919; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Programs, 1879-1903; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Artifacts, undated; Subseries 3.7; 1 item
    - Briefcase (empty), undated; 1 item (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Susan Gilmore Pierce, 1906-1918; Series 4.; 9 items
  Series IV., Susan Gilmore Pierce (Oct. 29, 1858-Oct. 1, 1918), is made up of 9 items (1906-1918) and is housed in one folder. Series IV consists of the few records in The Pierce Family Papers that were created by or collected by Susan Gilmore Pierce. This series is divided into 3 subseries: Incoming Letter, Financial Records, and Printed Material. The one incoming letter is from the Crane Company regarding an order for a foot bath. Financial records are 3 receipts. One receipt demonstrates Mrs. Pierce's interest in books while the other two receipts prove her membership in the Woodland Shakespeare Club and the Independent Order of Odd Fellows affiliated Rebekah Lodge No. 253. Printed material is made up of 3 yearbooks from the Woodland Shakespeare Club, a typed poem, and Mrs. Pierce's funeral notice.
  - Incoming Letter, June 2, 1913; Subseries 4.1.; 1 item
    - Crane Company, June 2, 1913; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 25.1)
  - Financial Records, 1906-1914; Subseries 4.2.; 3 items
    - Receipts, 1906-1914; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 25.2)
  - Printed Material, n.d., 1914-1918; Subseries 4.3.; 5 items
    - Yearbooks, Woodland Shakespeare Club, 1914-1916; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 25.3)
    - Funeral Notice, Susan Gilmore Pierce, Oct. 1, 1918; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 25.4)
    - Poem (typed), Grace Hazard Conkling, "After Sunset," n.d., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 25.5)
- George Gardner Pierce, 1901-1915; Series 5.; 0.25 ln. ft., 19 items
  Series V., George Gardner Pierce (Nov. 11, 1891-?), is made up of 19 items (1901-1915). Series V consists of records created by or collected by Gardner Pierce when he was a child and a young man. This series is divided into 4 subseries: Outgoing Telegram, Financial Records, Notes, and Printed Material. The Outgoing Telegram was the first ever sent by young Gardner to his father, George W. Pierce, Jr. Of the Financial Records, 3 of the account statements and receipts are for transactions between father and son while 2 are for Gardner's eyeglasses. Other financial records include two account books kept by Gardner when he was a university student. The Notes subseries includes a childhood note and lecture notes taken while a student at the University of California at Berkeley. Of interest among Gardner's lecture notes are such entries as "Fertilizers, U. C. Head Gardener's Suggestions" or "Cement pots, views and remarks by Mr. Priam." Primary school certificates of promotion and a 9th grade report card make up some of the Printed Material subseries. Two issues of the Woodland High School student publication, "The Ilex," round out the Printed Material subseries.
  - Outgoing Telegram, June 6, 1906; Subseries 5.1.; 1 item
    - Pierce, George W., Jr., June 6, 1906; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 26.1)
  - Financial Records, 1904-1915; Subseries 5.2.; 7 items
    - Account Statements and Receipts, 1904-1905; 5 items (Box 8, Folder 26.2)
    - Account Books, 1911-1915; 2 items
      - Account Book, 1 volume., 1911-1913; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Account Book, 1 volume., 1912-1915; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Notes, n.d., 1912-1913; Subseries 5.3.; 4 items
    - Lecture Notes, University of California, Berkeley, notebook and loose leaves., 1912-1913; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Note (in child's handwriting), n.d., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Printed Material, 1901-1911; Subseries 5.4.; 7 items
    - Certificates of Promotion, 1901-1906; 4 items (Box 8, Folder 31.1)
    - Report Card, 1904; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 31.2)
    - Student Publications, 1909-1911; 2 items
      - "The Ilex," Valentine Number, Woodland, CA: Woodland High School,., 1909; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - "The Ilex," Christmas Number, Woodland, CA: Woodland High School,., 1911; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Dixwell Lloyd Pierce, 1898-1940; Series 6.; 0.25 ln ft, 22 items
  Series VI., Dixwell Lloyd Pierce, is made up of 22 items (1898-1940) collected or created by Dixwell Pierce as a child or as an adult. This series is divided into 2 subseries: Correspondence and Printed Material.
  - Correspondence, 1908-1938; Subseries 6.1.; 8 items
    Dixwell Lloyd Pierce's correspondence is comprised of a small number of items that are divided into outgoing and incoming letters. The outgoing correspondence is made up of 2 drafts of a letter written by Dixwell (when he was a child) that may have been sent to the Perry Mason Company, Gold Coin Club. The incoming correspondence includes photocopies of letters sent to Pierce by Anna C. Markham (the wife of poet, Edwin Markham) and by the Markhams' son, Virgil Markham.
    - Outgoing Letters, drafts, 1908; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Incoming Letters, photocopies of 3 letters and 3 envelopes, 1927-1938; 6 items (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Printed Material, 1898-1940; Subseries 6.2.; 14 items
    This subseries is made up of printed material collected by Dixwell Lloyd Pierce. The printed materials are arranged by format and include a book; briefs, a judgment, and a petition; a certificate of promotion; clippings; a program; a report card; and student publications. One of the two student publications, the 1913 issue of Woodland High School's "The Ilex," features a photograph of Dixwell Pierce as part of "The Ilex" staff. Also of special interest are the briefs, judgment and petition. These 5 items relate to the formation of the Davis Joint Union High School District in Yolo County, CA and a 1924-25 court case (Civil No. 2907 in the District Court of Appeal of the State of California in and for the Third Appellate District) for which Dixwell Pierce acted as Attorney for Appellants. C. A. Covell, E. S. McBride, H. S. Lee (Superintendent of Schools of Yolo County, CA) were also among those involved in this case.
    - Book; Ainsworth, F. F., ed., "Hill's Vest-Pocket Rules of Order," Chicago, IL: Ogilvie and Company,., 1898; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Briefs, Judgment, and Petition relating to Civil No. 2907 in the District Court of Appeal of the State of California in and for the Third Appellate District, 1924-1925; 5 items (Box 8, Folder 37-39)
    - Certificate of Promotion, May 31, 1907; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Clippings (photocopies), Mr. and Mrs. Edwin Markham, n.d., 1938-1940; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Program, incomplete date, 1 item (Box 8, Folder 42.1)
    - Report card, 1914-1915; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 42.2)
    - Student Publications, 1913-1916; 2 items
      - "The Ilex," Commencement Number, Woodland, CA: Woodland High School,., 1913; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - "The Ilex," Commencement Number, Woodland, CA: Woodland High School,., 1916; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Pierce Family, 1852-1928; Series 7.; 0.5 ln. ft., 68 items
  Series VII., Pierce Family, contains 68 items (1852-1928) and takes up a half linear foot of space in an archives box, a folio box, and a document case. Materials included in the Pierce Family series were undoubtedly collected or created by members of the Pierce Family, but these items could not be identified as belonging to any certain family member. Series VII is divided into four subseries: Legal Document, Notes, Printed Material, and Artifact. The Legal Document is a single item, an 1852 contract for a schoolteacher. The Notes subseries consists of four handwritten note fragments and addresses. The Artifact subseries is made up of two empty checkbooks. The largest subseries is Printed Material. It has been arranged by the format of the printed materials: books, brochures, cards, clippings, fliers, funeral notices, ink blotters (several with advertisements), instructional materials for penmanship, newspapers, pamphlets, a typed poem, postcards, programs, a raffle ticket, schedules, sheet music, and a student publication. Some subjects covered by items in the printed material subseries include religion, household activities, penmanship, theatrical performances, and train routes. The 1910 pamphlet, "Pointers on Banking: Showing the Road to Independence and Wealth," features advertisements for Woodland, CA businesses.
  - Legal Document, Oct. 5, 1852; Subseries 7.1.; 1 item
    - Agreement between School District No. 1 in the town of Somers and Lucy French a qualified teacher of Somers, Oct. 5, 1852; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Notes, n.d., Subseries 7.2.; 4 items
    - Handwritten note fragments and addresses, n.d., 4 items (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Printed Material, 1852-1928; Subseries 7.3.; 61 items
    - Books, n.d., 1889-1925; 5 items
      - "The Cynic's Cyclopaedia," Boston, MA: Little, Brown, and Company,., 1925; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Hooker, H., "Child's Book on the Sabbath," New York: American Tract Society, n.d., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - "More Borrowings: A Compilation of Helpful Thoughts from Great Authors," San Francisco, CA: Murdock, C. A. and Company,., 1893; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Woolard, S. F., ed., "Good Fellowship," Wichita, KS: Goldsmith,., 1906; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Work, H. C., "Marching through Georgia," Boston, MA: Ticknor and Company,., 1889; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Brochures, n.d., 1887; 4 items (Box 8, Folder 52.1)
    - Bulletin; "The National Art Co.'s Frame and Premium Bulletin,"., 1876; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Cards, n.d., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 52.2)
    - Clippings, n.d., 1910-1918; 9 items (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Fliers, n.d., 3 items (Box 8, Folder 54.1)
    - Funeral Notices/Obituaries, 1883-1900; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 54.2)
    - Ink Blotters, n.d., 5 items (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Instructional materials for penmanship, n.d., 1870; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Newspapers, 1910-1923; 8 items
      - "The Daily Californian," vol. 1, no. 1, Berkeley, CA:., 1916; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - "The San Francisco Call.", 2 items (Box 11, Folder 13)
        May 7, 1910, pp. 1-2, 9-10 and May 8, 1910, pp. 29-40.
      - "The San Francisco Call.", 2 items (Box 11, Folder 14)
        May 10, 1910, pp. 1-18 and May 9, 1910, pp. 1-2, 13-14.
      - "The Sacramento Bee.", 2 items (Box 11, Folder 15)
        May 6, 1910, pp. 1-16 and May 10, 1910, pp. 1-20.
      - "The Sacramento Star,", pp. 9-10., [April 10, 1923]; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Pamphlets, 1852-1928; 7 items
      - Lothrop, J., "The Figurative Language of Scripture," ca.., 1852; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Newton, J. F., "The Music of Preaching: A Sermon, Preached in Trinity Church, in the City of Boston, on the Third Sunday in Advent, December 16, 1928, at a Service in Memory of Phillips Brooks," ca. 1928., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - "Pointers on Banking: Showing the Road to Independence and Wealth," Berkeley, CA:., 1910; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Sass, J., ed., "100 Up to Date and Popular Toasts," Detroit, MI: Sass Publishing Company, n.d., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 61)